<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Sandy Lake Dental</title>
    <link href="https://chandandentistry.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://chandandentistry.com" />
    <updated>1969-12-31T19:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Dr. Deveshi Chandan</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://chandandentistry.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Share Like and Follow</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dr. Deveshi Chandan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://chandandentistry.com/see-us-on/"/>
        <id>https://chandandentistry.com/see-us-on/</id>

        <updated>2020-06-26T01:09:34-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Give us a follow social media to stay updated on news and&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p class="align-center">Give us a follow social media to stay updated on news and announcements 🙂</p>
<p class="align-center"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/doctordenny81/">Facebook👍</a></p>
<p class="align-center"><a href="https://twitter.com/CharltonDental">Twitter🐤</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Testimonials</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dr. Deveshi Chandan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://chandandentistry.com/testimonials/"/>
        <id>https://chandandentistry.com/testimonials/</id>

        <updated>2020-06-26T01:09:34-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Dr. Charlton, thank you for taking good care of our basketball player.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <header>
<blockquote>
<p>Dr. Charlton, thank you for taking good care of our basketball player. Your generosity and professionalism by you and the entire staff is greatly appreciated.</p>
<p class="align-right">- Scott Weaver and the Reynolds Basketball Team</p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<p>Dr. Charlton, you deserve a BIG star! Words can not begin to explain how much I appreciate the great work and compassion you showed during my experience. The porcelain crowns on my six front upper teeth are beautiful and the partial plate matches them exactly and I have had absolutely no problems since the day they were finished. After years of covering my mouth and trying not to let anyone see my teeth, I am now smiling from ear to ear!”</p>
<p>Thanks so much!</p>
<p class="align-right">-Kim Andrews</p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<p>The Lakeview Girls’ Basketball Team would like to thank you for your continued support. Our program is successful because of your generosity!”</p>
<p class="align-right">- Lakeview Girls’ Basketball Players,<br>Coaches, Parents, and Boosters</p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<blockquote>
<p> </p>
</blockquote>
</header>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Our Dentists</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dr. Deveshi Chandan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://chandandentistry.com/about-the-dentists/"/>
        <id>https://chandandentistry.com/about-the-dentists/</id>

        <updated>2020-06-26T01:09:34-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     Dr. Dennis Charlton Dr. Dennis Charlton began his practice working evenings&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
    <h2 id="dr-dennis-charlton" class="align-center">
      Dr. Dennis Charlton
    </h2>

    <figure class="post__image post__image--center">
      <img loading="lazy" src="https://chandandentistry.com/media/posts/4/denny.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://chandandentistry.com/media/posts/4/responsive/denny-xs.jpg 300w ,https://chandandentistry.com/media/posts/4/responsive/denny-sm.jpg 480w ,https://chandandentistry.com/media/posts/4/responsive/denny-md.jpg 768w ,https://chandandentistry.com/media/posts/4/responsive/denny-lg.jpg 1024w"  height="243" width="180" alt="" />
      
    </figure>

  <p>
    <br>Dr. Dennis Charlton began his practice working evenings in the office of Dr. Herbert Gebert in Greenville, PA in July 1981. He opened his own office in a tiny space attached to the Mercer County State Bank in February of 1982. This tiny office had 2 operatories and 2 full time staff members.
<br>
<br>As the word spread of Dr. Charlton’s gentle demeanor and pleasant chair-side manner he continued to get busier. New staff needed to be added to enable the doctor to accommodate the patient flow. Through the 80’s he added two more full time staff as well as a part-time hygienist. In a very short time the practice grew beyond its doors and needed more room to grow. He built and moved into his new office just a block south of his original site in 1986. His new office sported 4 operatories and what looked like extra room for many years to come. He employed a full time hygienist and added other auxiliary staff to handle the flood of new patients. It did not take long for him to decide he needed to employ an associate and another full time hygienist to help handle the increasing patient database for such a small area.
<br>
<br>In 2002 four more operatories were added to accommodate 2 full time doctors and 2 full time hygienists. The Meadville office location was opened in July 2003. The supporting staff is a well blended mix of full and part-time employees. Charlton Dental Associates has strived to continue the same gentle, caring, and friendly office atmosphere that started the success back in 1981.
<br>
<br>The doctors are dedicated to their continuing education and maintaining a modern dental practice. Utilizing the most advanced technical skills and dental equipment available Dr. Charlton is able to acquire low radiation digital x-rays, produce same day porcelain crowns and inlays, place implants to secure dentures or replace individual teeth, and use laser technology to perform painless surgery and cavity preparation. The office has a reputation of being a friendly, caring practice that works hard at making a dental visit fun and stress free. Come in and visit and see for yourself!
  </p>

    <h2 id="dr-deveshi-chandan" class="align-center">
      Dr. Deveshi Chandan
    </h2>

    <figure class="post__image post__image--center">
      <img loading="lazy" src="https://chandandentistry.com/media/posts/4/doctor.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://chandandentistry.com/media/posts/4/responsive/doctor-xs.png 300w ,https://chandandentistry.com/media/posts/4/responsive/doctor-sm.png 480w ,https://chandandentistry.com/media/posts/4/responsive/doctor-md.png 768w ,https://chandandentistry.com/media/posts/4/responsive/doctor-lg.png 1024w"  height="640" width="640" alt="" />
      
    </figure>

  <p>
    Caring, compassionate and gentle is the reputation that precedes Dr. Deveshi Chandan, providing you with the best dental care possible. Dr. Chandan rather than rushing through the procedures, is thorough and you know that she is there to serve your needs and listen to you. She works closely with her patients creating a life long dental care plan which encourages daily attention to dental health and promotes healthy teeth and gums. She has a special affinity to children and makes them feel comfortable and interested in receiving dental care. Dr. Chandan is also passionate in serving the aging population with the dental care they deserve making them comfortable and trusting of oral health. She is diligent in her pursuit to stay up to date with the latest in dental procedures and state-of-the-art technology. She believes in preventative dentistry and is highly interested in aesthetic dentistry making your smile beautiful.
<br>
<br>Dr. Chandan obtained her Bachelors in Dental surgery from India. She then pursued her DMD from the University of Pittsburgh, School of Dental Medicine. During her schooling in Pittsburgh, she was passionate in serving the special needs patient population and was an active volunteer at the MOM (Mission of Mercy). She grew up in Toronto, Canada where she received education from the best schools and was a part of various multicultural community activities and charitable foundations. She is learning Spanish and is fluent in English, Hindi, Urdu, Gujarati and Punjabi.
<br>Outside of work, Dr. Chandan enjoys spending time with her three brothers and parents. She recently got married to her long term fiancée and best friend Gaurav Patel. They are a close knit family who enjoy going outdoors- kayaking, canoeing, fishing and camping. Her hobbies include dancing, singing, yoga and watching sports. She is passionate about advancing and supporting dentistry as a whole as a part of the local dental committee- PDA and the ADA.
<br>
<br>
  </p>

    <h2 id="dr-walter-thomas">
      Dr. Walter Thomas
    </h2>

  <p>
    Dr. Walter Thomas has been with Charlton Dental Assoicates for five years in both the Sandy Lake and Meadville offices. He resides at Conneaut Lake.
<br>
<br>Dr. Thomas has been practicing dentistry for over 33 years. He is a graduate of the University Of Pittsburgh School Of Dental Medicine, having an undergraduate degree from the University of Pittsburgh and a graduate degree from Duquesne University.
<br>
<br>Dr. Thomas began his dental career in private practice in Pittsburgh for his first 10 years. He was then Dental Director for a hospital program the next 18 years before joining Charlton Dental Associates five years ago.
<br>
<br>Dr. Thomas enjoys spending his free time in the Outer Banks of North Carolina. He loves spending time with family, especially his three children, daughter-in-law and grandson.
<br>
<br>Dr. Thomas likes to keep dentistry as relaxing as possible, so if you prefer, please call him Walt when you see him.
<br>
<br>He looks forward to seeing new patients and continuing the care for present patients.
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>About</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dr. Deveshi Chandan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://chandandentistry.com/about/"/>
        <id>https://chandandentistry.com/about/</id>

        <updated>2020-06-26T01:09:34-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     Charlton Dental Associates is proud to serve Sandy Lake &amp; Meadville,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    Charlton Dental Associates is proud to serve Sandy Lake &amp; Meadville, PA and surrounding areas. We are dedicated to providing the highest level of dental medicine along with friendly, compassionate service.
<br>
<br>If you have any questions about how we can care for your teeth &amp; mouth, please don’t hesitate to call us at (724) 376-7161 (Sandy Lake Office) or (814) 724-6890 (Meadville Office).
  </p>
<hr class="separator separator--dots" />
<div><div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" src="https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m14!1m8!1m3!1d5990.348144968526!2d-80.081123!3d41.34857!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x0%3A0x57cd3f09acb633fd!2sCharlton%20Dental%20Associates!5e0!3m2!1sen!2sus!4v1592869762451!5m2!1sen!2sus" width="400" height="300" frameborder="0" style="border:0;" allowfullscreen="" aria-hidden="false" tabindex="0"></iframe></div>
<div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" src="https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m14!1m8!1m3!1d11924.63165718207!2d-80.147525!3d41.65233!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x8832577e8926f1f1%3A0xbaa574a3ab64bee9!2s390%20Park%20Ave%2C%20Meadville%2C%20PA%2016335!5e0!3m2!1sen!2sus!4v1592869845270!5m2!1sen!2sus" width="400" height="300" frameborder="0" style="border:0;" allowfullscreen="" aria-hidden="false" tabindex="0"></iframe></div>
</div>

  <p>
    
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
